biotechinvfund.com 2010-02-10

# BiotechInvFund - Privacy Policy

At Bioaspects Inc (Biotechinvfund.com) we aim to protect your privacy as far as possible. We only use information that we collect about you to process transactions and to improve the quality of the service that we provide to you. 

#### The information we collect

The types of information that we collect include the following: 

  * In order to complete any applications or deals that you make we will need to know your name, email address ,and other related information. This is to allow us to complete your transaction and also to provide confirmation of the transaction to you. 
  * When you browse the service we will store information as to how you use the service in order to improve the quality of service provided to you. For example it will allow us to decide the most appropriate site layout and navigation. 
  * We also use the information we collect in order to inform you about changes to the service and occasionally other information that we think may be useful to you. If you inform us that you do not wish to receive such information we do not send it. 

#### Non disclose policy

We do not share information about our clients with any third parties for their independent use in marketing their products. We do not disclose nor do we reserve the right to disclose, any nonpublic personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone, except to other nonaffiliated third parties as required by law. 

#### Accessing and updating your personal information

You have the right to access your information at anytime to check whether it is accurate and up-to-date and should contact us if you wish to do so. 

#### Questions?

If you have any questions or complaints relating to the Privacy Policy or how we use the personal information we have about you, please contact us. We will endeavor to respond to you promptly. 

#### Glossary

A cookie is information that a web server stores on your hard disk so that it allows a web site to store your preferences on your machine and later retrieve it. 

A web bug is a graphic on a viewed web page that transmits information to a web server. 

An IP address is a 32-binary digit number that identifies each sender or receiver of information that is sent in packets across the Internet. 

A session is a series of interactions between two communication end points that occur during the span of a single connection and is related to a particular session number. 

Back
